I. M. Pei Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellany, 1920-2014 (Box 461-505)
  - Travel records (Box 495)
    - 2003 (Box 504)
      - May 8, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - May 14, London, England; Luxembourg; Berlin, Germany; Paris, France; Rome, Italy (Box 504)
      - July 8, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - July 30, Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 504)
      - Aug. 22, Martha’s Vineyard, Mass. (Box 504)
      - Sept. 6, London, England; Oare, England; Luxembourg; Berlin, Germany; Dresden, Germany (Box 504)
      - Sept. 24, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - Oct. 10, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - Oct. 21-22, Massachusetts (Box 504)
      - Oct. 27, Hong Kong; Suzhou Shi, China; Shanghai, China; Dawhah, Qatar; London, England; Paris, France (Box 504)
      - Jan. 2, Bermuda Islands (Box 504)
      - Mar. 3, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - Mar. 5, Bermuda Islands (Box 504)
      - Mar. 28, Paris, France; Luxembourg (Box 504)
      - Apr. 29, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - June 3, London, England; Paris, France (Box 504)
      - Aug. 5, Boston, Mass. (Box 504)
      - Sept. 2, Virginia; Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - Sept. 11, Dallas, Tex. (Box 504)
      - Sept. 26, Boston, Mass. (Box 504)
      - Nov. 6, Paris, France; Luxembourg; Rome, Italy; Naples, Italy (Box 504)
    - 2005 (Box 504)
      - Mar. 3, Bermuda Islands (Box 504)
      - Mar. 10, Boston, Mass. (Box 504)
      - Apr. 21, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - Apr. 27, London, England; Hong Kong; Suzhou Shi, China; Shanghai, China (Box 504)
      - July 3, Charlottesville, Va. (Box 504)
      - July 12, Washington, D.C. (Box 504)
      - Sept. 21, Paris, France; Luxembourg; Dawhah, Qatar (Box 505)
      - Nov. 7-9, San Francisco, Calif. (Box 505)
    - 2006 (Box 505)
      - Mar. 2, Bermuda Islands (Box 505)
      - Apr. 7, London, England; Luxembourg; Paris, France; Hong Kong; Suzhou Shi, China (Box 505)
      - June 20, Paris, France; Luxembourg; Norway (Box 505)
      - Sept. 16, Hong Kong; Suzhou Shi, China; Paris, France (Box 505)
      - Nov. 22, Paris, France; Dawhah, Qatar; Dubayy, United Arab Emirates (Box 505)
    - 2007 (Box 505)
      - Jan. 3, Dawhah, Qatar (Box 505)
      - Mar. 25, Paris, France; Malaga, Spain; Hong Kong; Kyoto, Japan; Tokyo, Japan (Box 505)
      - May 23, Washington, D.C. (Box 505)
      - June 2, Boston, Mass. (Box 505)
      - Oct. 25, Hong Kong; Kyoto, Japan; Dawhah, Qatar; Paris, France (Box 505)
    - 2008 (Box 505)
      - Jan. 17, Washington, D.C. (Box 505)
      - Mar. 8, Bermuda Islands (Box 505)
      - Apr. 14, London, England; Dawhah, Qatar; Paris, France; Provence, France (Box 505)
      - July 13, Washington, D.C. (Box 505)
      - July 29, Washington, D.C. (Box 505)
      - Nov., Paris, France; Dawhah, Qatar; London, England (Box 505)
    - 2009 (Box 505)
      - Mar. 7, Mexico (Box 505)
      - Apr. 3, Paris, France (Box 505)
      - July 9, Paris, France; Florence, Italy (Box 505)
      - Oct. 16, Boston, Mass. (Box 505)
      - Dec. 28, Costa Rica (Box 505)
    - 2010 (Box 505)
      - Feb. 8, New York; London, England; Hong Kong (Box 505)
      - July 16, Paris, France (Box 505)
    - 2011, Nov. 9, Hong Kong; Kyoto, Japan (Box 505)
    - 2012 (Box 505)
      - Mar. 26, Tokyo, Japan; Kyoto, Japan (Box 505)
      - May 15, Washington, D.C. (Box 505)
- Subject File, 1955-2012 (Box 505-534)
  Correspondence, along with reports, design books, and pamphlets document organizations and institutions to which Pei belonged and was an active member.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization and/or topic.
  - American Institute of Architects Task Forces (Box 505)
    - National Urban Policy (Box 505)
      - 1970 (Box 505)
      - 1971, (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 505, Box 506)
      - 1972, (7 folders); (2 folders) (Box 506, Box 507, Box 508)
      - 1973-1974, (5 folders) (Box 508)
    - West front of the United States Capitol (Box 509)
      - 1978, (4 folders) (Box 509)
      - 1979-1983, (4 folders) (Box 510)
  - Committee of 100 (Box 510)
    - 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 510)
    - 1991-1993, (6 folders) (Box 511)
    - 1994, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 511, Box 512)
    - 1995, (2 folders) (Box 512)
    - 1996, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 512, Box 513)
    - 1997-2000, (7 folders) (Box 513)
    - 2001-2005, (8 folders) (Box 514)
    - 2006-2012, (7 folders) (Box 515)
  - Juries (Box 516)
    - General (Box 516)
      - 1955-1971, (8 folders) (Box 516)
      - 1972-1983, (6 folders) (Box 517)
      - 1984-1986, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 517, Box 518)
      - 1987-1989, (5 folders) (Box 518)
      - 1990-2012, (5 folders) (Box 519)
    - National Gallery of Canada, Ottawa, Canada (Box 519)
      - 1976, (4 folders) (Box 519)
      - 1977, 1983, (2 folders) (Box 520)
    - Parliament House, Canberra, Australia (Box 520)
      - 1979, (4 folders); (6 folders); (1 folder) (Box 520, Box 521, Box 522)
      - 1980-1985, (6 folders) (Box 522)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Corp. (Box 522)
    - 1972, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 522, Box 523)
    - 1973, (2 folders) (Box 523, Box 524)
    - 1974, (3 folders) (Box 524)
    - 1975, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 524, Box 525)
    - 1976-1978, (7 folders) (Box 525)
    - 1979-1980, (5 folders) (Box 526)
    - 1981, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 526, Box 527)
    - 1982, (4 folders) (Box 527)
    - 1983, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 527, Box 528)
  - National Council on the Arts (Box 528)
    - 1980-1982, (4 folders) (Box 528)
    - 1983, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 528, Box 529)
    - 1984-1987, (5 folders) (Box 529)
  - National Council on the Humanities (Box 529)
    - 1966 (Box 529)
    - 1967-1970, (3 folders) (Box 530)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (Box 530)
    - 1973-1976, (4 folders) (Box 530)
    - 1981, (1 folder) (Box 530, Box 531)
    - 1982-1983, (2 folders) (Box 531)
    - 1984, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 531, Box 532)
    - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 532)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 532)
    - 1972-1984, (3 folders) (Box 532)
  - Urban Design Council of the City of New York (Box 532)
    - 1966, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 532, Box 533)
    - 1967-1969, (5 folders) (Box 533)
    - 1970-1972, (7 folders) (Box 534)
- Digital Files, 1995-2012
  Digital files are from digital storage media removed from paper files in the course of processing. A cross reference to the original location in the paper files is provided for each file. Request files using the Digital ID.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Projects Completed/Inactive
    - Photographs of the Weisner Building/Center for Arts and Media Technology, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 2007 (Container 153, Weisner Building...General), mss83787_123_017
    - Documents and spreadsheets containing details of pre-contract consultancy services, 2001-2002 (Container 273, Museum of Islamic Art...Ministry of Municipal Affairs and Agriculture), mss83787_123_040; mss83787_123_041
    - Drawing from the Ministry of Municipal Affairs and Agriculture Land Information Center, 2003 (Container 309, Museum of Islamic Art...Permitting), mss83787_123_039
    - Ronald Reagan UCLA Medical Center dedication television and radio media coverage, 2007 (Container 318, Ronald Reagan UCLA Medical Center, Topical files), mss83787_123_018; mss83787_123_019; mss83787_123_020
    - Video documentation of the construction progress of the Ronald Reagan UCLA Medical Center, as well as interviews and events surrounding the public opening, 2006-2008 (Container 318, Ronald Reagan UCLA Medical Center, Topical files), mss83787_123_021; mss83787_123_022; mss83787_123_023
    - Architectural drawings and plans of various wings and structures within the Grand Louvre, 1995-2006 (Container 354, Grand Louvre - General), mss83787_123_013
    - Files related to the twenty-year anniversary of the Grand Louvre pyramid opening, including videos of panel discussions, presentations, and a conversation with Pei, 2009 (Container 354, Grand Louvre...Twentieth anniversary of the pyramid), mss83787_123_016
  - Projects Aborted
    - Land surveys and drawing files related to Asia House, London, England, 1999 (Container 384, Asia House – Rand, Chris, file), mss83787_123_014
  - Projects Proposed
    - Land surveys and drawing files for the Kunsthistorisches Museum, Vienna, Austria, 1998 (Container 410, 1998 – Vienna, Austria), mss83787_123_044; mss83787_123_045; mss83787_123_046; mss83787_123_047; mss83787_123_048; mss83787_123_049
  - Publicity
    - Brief animated videos depicting construction of the National Gallery of Art East Wing, 2004 (Container 426, 2003, General), mss83787_123_050
    - Video of I. M. Pei being interviewed by Jack Pan on the television program 21@21, 2005 (Container 426, 2004, General), mss83787_123_029
    - Video of a conversation with I. M. Pei regarding the Museum of Islamic Art in Dahwah, Qatar, 2006 (Container 427, 2006, General), mss83787_123_026
    - Documentary, Yehudi Menuhin: Lord of the Strings, 2006 (Container 427, 2006, General), mss83787_123_027
    - Video of a conversation with I. M. Pei regarding the Musée d’Art Moderne Grand-Duc Jean in Luxembourg, 2006 (Container 427, 2006, General), mss83787_123_028
    - Documentary, Der alte Mann und der Kreis: I. M. Pei in Suzhou, 2007 (Container 428, 2007, General), mss83787_123_024; mss83787_123_025
    - Photograph of I. M. Pei and Fumihiko Maki, 2007 (Container 429, 2008, General), mss83787_123_042
    - Audio recording of I. M. Pei interview regarding Jean Dubuffet, 2009 (Container 430, 2009, General), mss83787_123_031
    - East-West Center, Honolulu, Hawaii, fiftieth anniversary video, 2010 (Container 430, 2009, General), mss83787_123_032
    - Episode of the television program Icon on CNN, featuring an interview with I. M. Pei at the Grand Louvre, 2010 (Container 431, 2010, General), mss83787_123_030
    - Selected scenes from the PBS American Masters episode, I.M. Pei: Building China Modern, 2010 (Container 431, 2010, General), mss83787_123_033
    - Photographs from CNN interview of I. M. Pei at the Grand Louvre, 2010, July 20 (Container 431, 2010, General), mss83787_123_043
    - Video of a conversation between I. M. Pei and architect John M. Johansen, 2011 (Container 432, 2011, General), mss83787_123_034
    - Video produced for the Foundation for Art and Preservation in Embassies award ceremony honoring I. M. Pei, 2012 (Container 432, 2012, General), mss83787_123_035
    - Video showing images of the Deutsches Historisches Museum, Berlin, Germany, 2004 (Container 433, Deutsches Historisches Museum), mss83787_123_036
    - Documentary, Kompliment, Mr. Pei!, 2004 (Container 433, Deutsches Historisches Museum), mss83787_123_037
    - Audio of I. M. Pei’s recollections of J. Carter Brown, 2002 (Container 443, Speaking engagements), mss83787_123_038
  - Miscellany
    - PowerPoint presentation of I. M. Pei’s major projects, 2003 (Container 485, Awards and honors...Henry C. Turner Prize for Innovation in Construction Technology...), mss83787_123_012
    - Photographs of I. M. Pei related to Laurea Honoris Causa award, 2004 (Container 486, Awards and honors...Laurea Honoris Causa...), mss83787_123_010; mss83787_123_011
    - Short videos paying tribute to I. M. Pei and other recipients of the Peopling of America Award, 2004 (Container 486, Awards and honors...Peopling of America Award...), mss83787_123_008
    - Videos of I. M. Pei being interviewed by architect David Adjaye, 2010 (Container 486, Awards and honors...Royal Gold Medal for Architecture...), mss83787_123_004; mss83787_123_006; mss83787_123_007
    - Videos of the Royal Gold Medal ceremony and dinner, including the presentation of the award to I. M. Pei, his acceptance speech, and tributes from colleagues, 2010 (Container 486, Awards and honors...Royal Gold Medal for Architecture...), mss83787_123_005
    - Video produced for the Foundation for Art and Preservation in Embassies award ceremony honoring I. M. Pei, 2012 (Container 487, Awards and honors...Annenberg Award for Diplomacy through the Arts...), mss83787_123_035
    - Photographs and drawings of Oare Pavilion, Wiltshire, England, 2003 (Container 490, Exhibitions - General), mss83787_123_037
    - Video produced to commemorate Tunghai University fiftieth anniversary, 2002 (Container 491, Honorary degrees...Tunghai University), mss83787_123_001
- Oversize, 1958-2009 (Box OV 1-OV 49)
  Architectural drawings and plans, blueprints, certificates, maps, photographs, brochures and other printed matter, and a letter, scroll, watercolor drawing, and diploma.
  Listed and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the material was removed. Physically grouped and housed by size of the items, with containers numbered sequentially according to the physical arrangement.
  - General Correspondence
    - Scroll with a quotation by Sun Yat-Sen, presented by T. C. Tsao, 1958 (Container 4, "R-T" general) (Box OV 30)
    - Photographs of Pablo Picasso and sculptures by the artist taken by Carl Nesjar, undated (Container 21, Nesjar, Carl) (Box OV 45)
    - Letter from Robert Chesley Osborn after a tour of the East Building of the National Gallery of Art, Washington, D.C., 1978 (Container 43, Osborn) (Box OV 1)
    - Watercolor and ink drawing of a traditional landscape sent by Y. Z. Pei, 1979 (Container 50, Chinese correspondence) (Box OV 17)
  - Projects Completed/Inactive
    - Annapolis, Md., St. John's College, poster presentation with campus plan, aerial photograph of the campus, and a drawing of a building exterior, undated (Container 136, Annapolis) (Box OV 14)
    - Barcelona, Spain, La Caixa Bank Headquarters
      - Presentation drawings, 1992 (Container 136, La Caixa) (Box OV 17)
      - Blueprints, 1994 (Container 137, La Caixa) (Box OV 17)
        - Vols. I and IIA (Box OV 17)
        - Vols. IIB and III (Box OV 18)
    - Beijing, China, Bank of China Head Office, boxed set of presentation drawings, 1995 (Container 137, Bank of China) (Box OV 1)
    - Berlin, Germany, Deutsches Historisches Museum, two sets of presentation drawings, 1997 (Container 142, Topical files) (Box OV 2)
    - Boston, Mass., John F. Kennedy Library, copy of site plans with pencil annotations, 1972 (Container 147, General) (Box OV 18)
    - Brooklyn, N.Y., Bedford-Stuyvesant Superblock, award certificate, 1974 (Container 151, General) (Box OV 2)
    - Cambridge, Mass., Gateway to Guilford North Point, spiral-bound set of presentation drawings and model photographs, 1999 (Container 152, Gateway) (Box OV 2)
    - Chicago, Ill., University Gardens Apartments, bound set of presentation drawings for Hyde Park redevelopment project, circa 1959 (Container 153, Chicago) (Box OV 3)
    - Cleveland, Ohio, Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, spiral-bound set of presentation drawings, 1987 (Container 155, Topical files) (Box OV 3)
    - Columbus, Ind., Cleo Rogers Memorial Library, plans, 1985 (Container 155, Columbus) (Box OV 31)
    - Dallas, Tex., Morton H. Meyerson Symphony Center, certificate of recognition, 1990 (Container 159, General) (Box OV 18)
    - Dawhah, Qatar, Museum of Islamic Art
      - Chin, Perry
        - Set of drawings, 2003 (Container 251, Architectural detail drawings) (Box OV 19)
        - Set of drawings detailing the exterior of the building, 2003 (Container 251, Architectural drawings and exterior enclosure) (Box OV 19)
        - Bound set of detail drawings, 2003 (Container 251, Architectural drawings, base building), (1 folder) (Box OV 19, Box OV 20)
        - Drawings for auditorium, 2003 (Container 251, Auditorium design drawings) (Box OV 20)
        - Hand and computer-generated renderings of exterior and interior, 2002 (Container 254, Concept designs) (Box OV 32)
        - Two spiral-bound dossiers containing graphic designs from other museums and sketch designs for the Museum of Islamic Art, 2004 (Container 255, Corporate identity designs) (Box OV 3)
        - Three sets of mechanical, plumbing, and engineering drawings, 2003 (Container 256, Electrical, plumbing, and ventilation), (3 folders) (Box OV 21)
        - Set of drawings for the central courtyard and fountain, 2003 (Container 258, Fountain drawing sheets) (Box OV 22)
        - Two spiral-bound, graphic-design dossiers containing preliminary and sketch designs, 2004 (Container 258, Graphic designs) (Box OV 4)
        - Bound set of drawings for exterior stone system, 2003 (Container 260, Interior and exterior stone cladding) (Box OV 20)
        - Interior drawings, 2001-2004 (Container 260, Interior architectural design) (Box OV 22)
        - Landscape drawings, 2006 (Container 268, Landscape layouts and details), (1 folder) (Box OV 23, Box OV 24)
        - Bound set of early drawings, 2002 (Container 277, Preliminary design issue) (Box OV 20)
        - Set of preliminary security design drawings, 2004 (Container 284, Security design) (Box OV 4)
        - Three spiral-bound dossiers on signage, including investigation, sketch designs, and bid documents, 2004-2005 (Container 289, Signage), (3 folders) (Box OV 5)
        - Site maps, 2000-2004 (Container 289, Site plans) (Box OV 33)
        - Two sets of drawings, 2003-2004 (Container 293, Structural drawing sheets) (Box OV 24)
      - Okamoto, Hiroshi
        - Working drawings, 2002 (Container 310, Preliminary design), (3 folder); (2 folder) (Box OV 14, Box OV 15)
      - Topical files (Box OV 15)
        - Three sets of presentation drawings, 2001-2003 (Container 313, Presentation material), (1 folder) (Box OV 15, Box OV 16)
    - Luxemburg, Luxembourg, Musée d'Art Moderne Grand-Duc Jean, two sets of presentation drawings, 1996 (Container 320, General) (Box OV 6)
    - New York, N.Y.
      - 88 Pine St. (Wall Street Plaza), award certificate, 1973 (Container 328, 88 Pine) (Box OV 6)
      - Four Seasons Hotel renovation, shop drawings (Container 338, Shop drawings)
        - Zoning and architectural drawings, 1990, 2000-2002, (1 folder) (Box OV 34, Box OV 35)
        - Presentation drawings, 2000-2001 (Box OV 46)
        - Architectural drawings, 1989-1991, 2001, (3 rolls) (Box OV 46)
        - Marino, Peter, interior drawings, 2001-2002, (3 rolls) (Box OV 47)
        - Structural and electrical drawings, 2000-2003 (Box OV 47)
        - Burgess Steel and Petrillo Stone, 2001-2003 (Box OV 48)
          - Burgess Steel, (4 rolls) (Box OV 48)
          - Petrillo Stone (Box OV 48)
        - Precast façade and windows, 1990-1992, (3 rolls) (Box OV 49)
        - HVAC drawings, 1991-1993, (2 rolls) (Box OV 49)
    - Paris, France
      - Le Grand Louvre, early plans for the pyramid, 1984 (Container 349, General) (Box OV 36)
      - Tête de la Défense, plans, 1970-1973 (Container 360, General), (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box OV 28, Box OV 29)
    - Shiga, Japan
      - Miho Institute of Aesthetics chapel (Container 362, Team files)
        - Hand sketches and design drawings, circa 2006-2009 (Box OV 25)
        - Design drawings and renderings, 2006-2009, (2 folders) (Box OV 25)
      - Miho Museum
        - Certificate of recognition, 1996 (Container 364, General) (Box OV 6)
        - Spiral-bound set of presentation drawings for building design and landscape concepts, 1997 (Container 365, Topical files) (Box OV 6)
    - Suzhou Shi, China, City Planning project (Container 371, City Planning)
      - Book, Planning Controls and Preservation of Historical Residential Blocks in Suzhou, and two bound volumes of urban plans and site drawings, 1988, circa 1995, (2 folders) (Box OV 7)
      - Bound and printed report of the Suzhou International Planning Workshop for the Ping Jiang District Renovation and Redevelopment Plan, 1996 (Box OV 8)
      - Certificate of appointment as senior advisor, 1996 (Box OV 26)
      - Large decorative map of Suzhou, China, perhaps given as a gift, circa 1995 (Box OV 37)
      - Series of maps of Suzhou, China, 1995, undated (Box OV 38)
    - Washington, D.C., East Building of the National Gallery of Art, presentation drawings, undated (Container 340, General) (Box OV 39)
    - Wiltshire, England, Oare Pavilion
      - Plans and drawings, 2000 (Container 375, Chin, Perry) (Box OV 40)
      - Spiral-bound set of presentation drawings, 2000 (Container 376, Client correspondence) (Box OV 8)
  - Projects Aborted
    - Athens, Greece, Athens Museum of Contemporary Art, spiral-bound set of presentation drawings, 1993 (Container 377, General) (Box OV 16)
    - Bilbao, Spain, Bilbao Emblematic Building
      - Boxed set of presentation drawings, 1995 (Container 381, General) (Box OV 9)
      - Portfolio of presentation drawings and photographs of models, 1991 (Container 381, General) (Box OV 10)
    - La Rochefoucauld, France, Château de La Rochefoucauld, spiral-bound set of presentation drawings, 1999 (Container 383, General) (Box OV 10)
    - Osaka, Japan, China Pavilion at Expo '70
      - Two bound sets of blueprints, 1969 (Container 385, General), (2 folders) (Box OV 26)
      - Drawings with notes and annotations, 1969 (Container 386, Topical files) (Box OV 41)
    - San Francisco, Calif., Ferry Building, spiral-bound set of drawings, circa 1980 (Container 386, Ferry) (Box OV 16)
  - Projects Proposed
    - 1973, Paris, France, Jean Dubuffet project, pencil sketch of site on an envelope, 1975 (Container 393, Drawings and plans) (Box OV 10)
    - 2001, miscellaneous, portfolio of color photographs of Westside, Los Angeles, Calif., attached to a letter from Michael S. Ovitz, 2001 (Container 411, Miscellaneous) (Box OV 10)
  - Publicity
    - General
      - Series of interviews in Ming Pao Weekly, 1988 (Container 417, 1988-1992) (Box OV 11)
      - Article on Pei from Le Figaro, 1993 (Container 417, 1993) (Box OV 27)
      - Color photographic portrait of Pei by Richard Schulman for Portraits of the New Architecture, 2004 (Container 427, 2004) (Box OV 11)
    - Projects
      - Commemorative booklet, 1979 (Container 434, John F. Kennedy Library) (Box OV 11)
      - Wall calendar featuring skyscraper buildings, including the John Hancock Tower, Boston, Mass., and the Bank of China Tower, Hong Kong, 1999 (Container 435, Bank of China Tower) (Box OV 11)
      - Marked-up galley proof of commemorative book, 1997 (Container 440, Miho Museum) (Box OV 11)
      - Wall calendars, "Miho Museum: The Architecture of I. M. Pei," with photographs by Kiyohiko Higashide, 1999, 2003 (Container 441, Miho Museum) (Box OV 42)
  - Miscellany
    - Architectural registrations
      - Certificate of registration, Singapore, 1976 (Container 479, Singapore) (Box OV 12)
      - Certificates of registration, Connecticut, Colorado, Delaware, and the District of Columbia, 1957-1964 (Container 479, Alabama-Florida) (Box OV 12)
      - Certificates of registration, Georgia, Indiana, Iowa, Hawaii, Massachusetts, and Michigan, 1960-1974 (Container 479, Georgia-Michigan) (Box OV 12)
      - Certificates of registration, New Jersey and Nebraska, 1972 (Container 479, Missouri-North Carolina) (Box OV 12)
      - Certificates of registration, Oklahoma, Pennsylvania, and Tennessee, 1959-1974 (Container 480, Ohio-Tennessee) (Box OV 12)
      - Certificates of registration, Texas and Virginia, 1966, 1971 (Container 480, Texas-Wisconsin) (Box OV 12)
    - Awards and honors
      - Award certificates from the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, American Conservatory Theater, American Institute of Architects, District of Columbia Redevelopment Land Agency, Federal Housing Administration, National Academy of Design, and Urban Renewal Administration, 1963-1969 (Container 480, 1960s, miscellaneous), (7 folders) (Box OV 12)
      - Award certificate from the Citizens Union of the City of New York, 1969 (Container 480, 1960s, miscellaneous) (Box OV 13)